International Communist Front Organization Additional Publications 5725
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Communist Front Organization Additional Publications
1973-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Communist Front Organization
5725
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
5697003
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5033: International Communist Front Organizations Monthly Publications and Miscellaneous Publications
Communism -- United States; International Communist Front Organization.
5697003
- International Communist Front Organizations, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Newsletter
  - Item 1: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 263 (1973: January). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 264 (1973: February). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 265 (1973: March). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 266 (1973: April). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 267 (1973: May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 268 (1973: June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 269 (1973: July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 270 (1973: August). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 271 (1973: September). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 272 (1973: October). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 273 (1973: November). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    no. 274 (1973: December). Item is in English.
- International Communist Front Organizations, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 275 (1974: January). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 276 (1974: February). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 277 (1974: March). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 278 (1974: April). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 279 (1974: May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 280 (1974: June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 281 (1974: July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 282 (1974: August). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 283 (1974: September). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 284 (1974: October). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 285 (1974: November). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    no. 286 (1974: December). Item is in English.
- International Communist Front Organizations, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 287 (1975: January). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 288 (1975: February). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 289 (1975: March). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 290 (1975: April). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 291 (1975: May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 292 (1975: June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 293 (1975: July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 294 (1975: August). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 295 (1975: September). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 296 (1975: October). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 297 (1975: November). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    no. 298 (1975: December). Item is in English.
- International Communist Front Organizations, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 299 (1976: January). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 300 (1976: February). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 301 (1976: March). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 302 (1976: April). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 303 (1976: May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 304 (1976: June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 305 (1976: July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 306 (1976: August). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 307 (1976: September). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 308 (1976: October). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 309 (1976: November). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    no. 310 (1976: December). Item is in English.
- International Communist Front Organizations, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 311 (1977: January). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 312 (1977: February). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 313 (1977: March). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 314 (1977: April). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 315 (1977: May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 316 (1977: June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 317 (1977: July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 318 (1977: August). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 319 (1977: September). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 320 (1977: October). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 321 (1977: November). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    no. 322 (1977: December). Item is in English.
- International Communist Front Organizations, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    no. 323 (1978: January). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    no. 324 (1978: February). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    no. 325 (1978: March). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    no. 326 (1978: April). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    no. 327 (1978: May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    no. 328 (1978: June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: International Communist Front Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    no. 329 (1978: July). Item is in English.
- Trends in Communist International Organizations, 1978-1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1978: July/August. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1978: August/September. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1978: September/October. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1978: November/December. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1978: October/November. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    1978: December/1979: January. Item is in English.
- Trends in Communist International Organizations, 1979-1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: March/April. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: April/May. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: May/June. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: June/July. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: July/August. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: August/September. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: September/October. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    1979: December/1980: January. Item is in English.
- Trends in Communist International Organizations, 1980-1981; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: January/february. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: February/March. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: March/April. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: April/May. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: May/june. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: June/July. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: July/August. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: August/September. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: October/November. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: November/December. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1980: December/1981: January. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Trends in Communist International Organisations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1981: January/February. Item is in English.